

I'm an innovative software engineer & leader, with a knack for UI/X design. I specialize in building consumer-facing mobile applications, as-well-as the SDK's & libraries that support them. With 10+ years of experience, I can turn things on their heads, think outside the box, and above all else - put usability and simplicity at the center of my development process.

# **Education**

2013 | BS

#### **COMPUTER SCIENCE**

Central Washington University

2011 | AA

#### NATURAL SCIENCE

Green River Community College

# **Skills & Highlights**

- Swift, Objective-C, C++, C#, Node.js, TypeScript, Nest.js, Vapor, & Go experience
- iOS, iPadOS, watchOS, tvOS, visionOS & Android platform knowledge
- Modern architecture using MVVM, DI, & reactive frameworks (Combine / Rx)
- Modern dependency management using SPM & Cocoapods
- CI automation (Github Actions, Xcode Server, Fastlane, & Jenkins)
- Experience leading & scaling engineering teams
- Startup, B2B, & M&A experience
- Coffee snob **Yes**, this is a skill  $\textcircled{\bullet}$

# **Experience**

2023 - PRESENT

#### **LEAD IOS ENGINEER**

#### FISKER | MANHATTAN BEACH, CA | APP STORE | PLAY STORE

Developed & maintained the Fisker iOS application & core libraries. Lead the team's transition to a modern architecture using SwiftUI, Combine, MVVM, DI, services, & navigators.

2023 - 2024

# ENGINEERING LEAD

# WING | LOS ANGELES, CA

Lead a team of engineers across mobile, backend, & frontend web. Architected the Wing tech-stack, iOS application, & support libraries. Work with SLT on brand, design, investment, & marketing efforts.

2019 - 2023

#### **MOBILE LEAD**

# AIRVET | LOS ANGELES, CA | APP STORE | PLAY STORE

Lead a team of mobile engineers across both iOS & Android platforms. Architected the Airvet parent & doctor iOS applications & support libraries. Worked closely with product, design, & SL teams for roadmap & product planning.

2018 - 2019

# SR. IOS ENGINEER

## **AUTOGRAVITY** | IRVINE, CA

Developed & maintained first-party and white-label applications, libraries, & tools. Managed iOS release automation & CI pipeline.

2016 - 2018

## **SR. IOS ENGINEER**

# TV TIME / WHIPCLIP | SANTA MONICA, CA | APP STORE | PLAY STORE

Developed & maintained the Whipclip iOS application, as well as the project's transition into TV Time; via company acquisition. Led the migration effort from Objective-C  $\rightarrow$  Swift. Worked alongside product and design teams for a complete re-branding & UI/X overhaul.

2015 - 2016

# LEAD IOS ENGINEER

## **FUSION OF IDEAS** | LAKE FOREST, CA

Lead a team of mobile engineers across both iOS & Android platforms. Developed & maintained iOS B2B applications and underlying frameworks for several high-profile clients.



**E** mitchtreece@me.com **P** 253.906.0972

Made with ♥ in Los Angeles, CA 😎

